JULY 15TH (THURS) 10:43 AM
YES! THIS GIG'S IN THE BAG!
TIME TO MAKE SOME MONEY!
ROHAN KISHIBE MUST BE LOADED.
I'M GONNA MAKE A KILLING.
I'll JUST CHARGE A LITTLE BIT MORE
AND HOPE HE BITES.
I HATE IT WHEN PEOPLE
LOOK AT MY BACK.
I REALLY DON'T WANT ANYONE
PEEKING AT MY BACK.
IT'S NOT LIKE I HAVE ZITS OR
WEIRD SCARS OR A TATTOO,
I JUST DON'T WANT ANYBODY
LOOKING AT MY BACK!
I CAN'T GET A GIRLFRIEND.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?!
JULY 15TH (THURS) 9:06 AM
EPISODE 32
JULY 15TH (THURS), PART 2
MORIOH LANDMARK NO. 9:
THE MAN IN THE ELECTRICAL TOWER
JULY 15TH (THURS) 10:58 AM
JULY 15TH (THURS) 11:16 AM
SHINING DIAMOND
JULY 15TH (THURS) 10:20 AM
JULY 15TH (THURS) 11:37 AM
SNIFF
JULY 15TH (THURS) 12:05 PM
JULY 15TH (THURS) 12:28 PM
JULY 15TH (THURS) 7:37 AM
THESE ARE YOUR PANTIES
GULP
TOMOKO HIGASHIKATA
KOICHI HIROSE
BA-DUMP
EPISODE 33
JULY 15TH (THURS), PART 3